hackerzcity.com 2013-08-06

# Hackerzcity - Privacy

Your usage of this website constitutes your agreement to the following terms.

Hackerzcity is Legal 

*) Hackerzcity not hosted any of Copyright Content in our website Nor upload and Download Content Avilable Here is Proof :-http://www.siteadvisor.com/sites/hackerzcity.com

*) Hackerzcity Hosting on Top class hosting service 0 Torerance of Copyright Content 

*) The images avilable on hackerzcity are embed code we not hosted that images They are uploded in other other server 

*) We do-not share Any hacking information not doing any discusion about Hacking . It's a Discusion forum Soprts/show/Account

*) Videos Avilable on hackerzcity are embed from youtube and dailymotion We not hosting any videos on hackerzcity

*) We are not embed live stream nor we showing Live stream on hackerzity 

Premium Account Sections

We are not associated with any file hosting service/website present on this website.

We do not use illegal ways of getting hold of the resources present on this website.

We take no responsibility relating the use of the resources present on this website.

We cannot be held responsible if You misuse the resources present on this website.

You may not use this website to distribute or download any material when you do not have the legal rights to do so.

It is your responsibility as a moral person to know if You have the right or not to use the resources present on this website.

If you are unsure or if You do not have the right to use the resources present on this website, please do not use the resources present on this website.

We take no responsibility for what You upload/download by using the resources present on this website.

The content shared by using the resources present on this website is not hosted on this website.

The Owner of this website cannot be held responsible for any actions performed by its users.

The sole purpose of this website is to regroup all the resources on one page and to promote file sharing services to new users.

It is your own responsibility to adhere to these terms.

If you are the owner of any website present on this website and you wish that we stop promoting your service, simply contact us and we will remove any content related to your website.

Our Commitment hackerzcity.com is strongly committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information secure. To earn your trust and confidence in our commitment, we are fully disclosing our privacy practices. We encourage you to read our privacy statement to understand what types of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use this information.

Information collected by hackerzcity.com and how it is used hackerzcity.com only collects the necessary personally identifiable information in order to respond to your requests for our customized products and services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, birth date, and any other information that itself identifies or when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual.

This website does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. hackerzcity.com and its service partners use your personally identifiable information to operate the sites and services and to inform you of new features, services, and products from hackerzcity.com and its affiliates.

hackerzcity.com may also carefully select other companies to send you information about their products or services which are related to the site’s service but are not necessary to its operation (an “Extended Service”). If hackerzcity.com intends to use personally identifiable information for an Extended Service, the hackerzcity.com site will provide you with the ability and requisite instructions to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of informational or promotional mail from hackerzcity.com by following the instructions on the mail.

hackerzcity.com may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the site or its owners; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the site-owners, the site or the users of hackerzcity.com, and (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of hackerzcity.com, the site, its owners, or the public.

User/member interaction features hackerzcity.com has many features that provide for users/members to disclose their identities and communicate with other users/members. Your use of such features and disclosure of any personal details (e.g. e-mail address) by you through these features are at your sole risk and hackerzcity.com accepts no responsibility for the same. However, if your privacy has been intruded as a result of participating in such features, you could notify us by e-mail at privacy@hackerzcity.com.

Other Websites The hackerzcity.com site contains links to other websites. hackerzcity.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.  
Notify Us   
If at any time you believe that hackerzcity.com or its users/members have not adhered to these principles, please notify hackerzcity.com by e-mail at privacy@hackerzcity.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.
